{
    "subject": "resource/Langenthal",
    "predicate": "ontology/twinTown",
    "object": "resource/Brig-Glis",
    "human_readable": "The twin town of Langenthal is Brig-Glis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9677855372428894,
            "question": "Name the twin town of Langenthal."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9609645009040833,
            "question": "Is Brig-Glis a twin town?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.938951849937439,
            "question": "Which town is Brig-Glis twinned with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9171280264854431,
            "question": "What is the twin town of Langenthal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.91036456823349,
            "question": "If Langenthal is a town, what can you say about Brig-Glis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7660248875617981,
            "question": "Are Langenthal and Brig-Glis connected in some way?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7387677431106567,
            "question": "What relationship exists between Langenthal and Brig-Glis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3195997178554535,
            "question": "What does it mean for two towns to be twinned?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22931738197803497,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a twin town relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19675196707248688,
            "question": "What are some potential benefits of having twin towns?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The twin town of Langenthal is Brig-Glis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5761_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a twin town relationship?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5761_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does it mean for two towns to be twinned?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5761_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What relationship exists between Langenthal and Brig-Glis?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5761_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5761_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5761_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5761_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5761_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5761_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5761_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5761_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5761_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5761_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5761_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context information provided shows that the document `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5761/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt` mentions \"Langenthal \u21c4\" in relation to Brig-Glis, indicating a twin town relationship. Therefore, the statement \"The twin town of Langenthal is Brig-Glis\" is supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}